Lina Xu

Cell: 541-602-7435 E-Mail: xulin@onid.orst.edu 707 SW 10th St. Apt 314 Corvallis, OR 97333

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Operational Management, Business Process Management, Financial Accounting, Managerial Accounting, Entrepreneurship, Statistical Inference

KEY STRENGTHS SUMMARY

Good Ability of Manage People: wrote some proposals about how to manage employees to my father and helped my father manage his employees.

Billinguals: Intermediate English and Fluent Chinese

Strong Communication Skill: Experienced salesperson with one month. Prove ability to strong communicate, hard-working and ability to interface and influence different levels of customers, profits increase by 5%.

Strong Affinity: worked waitress in one month. Provided patient and friendly attitude to customers, they would like picked me as their server.

EDUCATION

Oregon State University Corvallis, Oregon

Anticipated

September

Gratiation: June 2015

Bachelor of Science Management

OSU Cumulative 3.12

INTO Oregon State University Corvallis, OR

2011- September 2012

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

QingZuTang

QingHuangDao, HeBei July 2013 to August 2014

Cashier; Lobby Ambassador

 Checked the bill or money, recorded accounts, matched the money and accounts and turned in money to manager Introduced the products, promoted monthly specials brought a positive attitude to work with a bright smile.

JianShanJiao QingHuangDao,

HeBei June 2012 to July 2012

Salesperson

 Checked the bill or money, recorded numbers of clothes in the store and selling, introduced the clothes, provided friendly and patient personality to communicate with customers, handled complex problems with customers.

COMMUNITY SERVICE

Chinese student Association (CSA) at the China Night Event Girls and Boys Club Play with and take care their safety Healthy Eating Cooking Event June 2012 2010-2013 October 2013

HONORS/AWADS

• Honor Roll, Oregon State University, Recipient of Winter 2014